Register of the Stanley Kuhl Hornbeck papers, 1900-1966
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject and Correspondence File, 1842-1966 (Boxes 1-452)
  - Far East
    - Bibliography
      - China (Box 162)
        - Special of ten books, 1922 October 20
        - Tables of contents
        - Tariff
        - Trade, Commerce, and Industry
      - France
        - Colonial Administration
        - Consortium
      - Japan
        - Comprehension
        - Industrial development
        - Industries
        - New bibliography to 1922
        - Selected book list, 1918
        - Tables of contents
      - Korea
      - Magazines, 1916-1917
      - Newark Public Library lists
      - Siam
    - Bulletin (Box 163)
    - Burma
    - Canadian's view
    - "The Changing East," by Marcossan
    - China
    - Commercial
    - Conditions and special memoranda
    - Courses in American colleges
    - Culture
    - Dutch East Indies
    - Economic
    - Immigration to Canada
    - India, political and economic conditions, 1923
    - Institute of Far Eastern Affairs, American University, 1932 March 21
    - League of Nations
    - Literature
    - Loans
    - Monroe Doctrine
    - Naval, Koch, 1923
    - Naval strategy in Pacific
    - Naval War College, 1928
    - Policy
    - Policy for
    - Policy Problems
    - Policy, Seward's by Dennett
    - Policy of the United States
    - Article regarding political unrest in 1923 by Charles Hodges, The Annalist Annual, 1924 January 7
    - Press clippings, 1922
    - Public and private financial problems, 1922 (Box 164)
    - Publicity
    - Quigley's outline
    - Reinsch on, 1921
    - Remaining questions to Grew for Polk, 1919 August
    - Russia
    - Russian policy
    - Secret Treaties of 1917
    - Shippings
    - Solutions
    - Tariff notes
    - Tibet
    - Tibet, treaties
    - Trade
    - Trade, American prospects for, 1923
    - Trade methods
    - U.S. Diplomacy in Far East
    - U.S. Far Eastern Relations, Gulick
    - U.S. in Orient
    - War College
  - Far Eastern Advisory Commission
  - Far Eastern Association
  - Far Eastern Bureau, policy
  - Far Eastern Division, personnel, circa 1947
  - Far Eastern Newsletter
  - Far Eastern Policy, World Peace Foundation Trustees, 1937 October 16
  - Far Eastern Quarterly
  - Far Eastern Republic
  - Far Eastern Review
  - Far Eastern Studies
  - Far Eastern Survey
  - Farago, Ladislas
  - Farish, F. Paul
  - Farley, James A.
  - Farnum, George R. (Box 165)
  - Farrar and Rinehart
  - Farrell, James
  - Farrington, J. R. (Delegate from Hawaii)
  - Farrington, Joseph R.
  - Farrington, Mrs. J. R.
  - Farrington, W. R.
  - Farrior, Mrs. S. C.
  - Fassett, Max
  - Feary, Robert A.
  - Federal Bar Association
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation
  - Federal City Club
  - FCC Monitoring Service, general broadcasts
  - Federal Council of the Churches, 1949
  - Federal Reserve Bank of New York
  - Federal Reserve, J. Jenks
  - Federal Union
  - Federation of Europe
  - Feffer, Dr. James I., 1965
  - Feilchenfeld, E. H. and Holohan, W. V.
  - Feiler, Arthur
  - Feis, Herbert
  - Fellers, Nancy Jane (Box 166)
  - Fengtien Law College
  - Fennell, Gerald M.
  - Fenwick, Charles G.
  - Ferguson, Homer (Senator of Michigan)
  - Ferguson, Homer, on China, Formosa, etc., 1950
  - Ferguson, Dr. J. C.
  - Ferrell, Robert, notes, memos, etc.
  - Ferrell, Robert H., 1966
  - Ferrin, Augustin W.
  - Ferrin, Dana H.
  - Field, Frederick V., Amerasia
  - Field, Frederick V.
  - Field, Dr. G. W.
  - Field, Henry
  - Fifth column
  - Finance, world, after war
  - Financial
  - Finch, George A.
  - Finch, John W.
  - Fine, Louis E.
  - Finland
  - Finold, Rudy H., 1964
  - First National Bank of Ordway
  - Firuski, Mrs. Elizabeth B.
  - Fischer, Colonel Arthur F.
  - Fischer, Louis
  - Fish, Ben
  - Fish, Hamilton (New York)
  - Fishel, Wesley R.
  - Fisher, Galen M.
  - Fisher, William Dale
  - Fisheries
  - Fisk, Sir Ernest
  - Fitch, George A. (Box 167)
  - Fitch, Geraldine
  - Fitch, Robert F.
  - Fitch, T. F.
  - Flag, U.S. ceremonial
  - Fleisher, B. W.
  - Fleming, D. F.
  - Fleming, Jackson
  - Fleming, Lamar
  - Fletcher, William G.
  - Florida, University of, Wilgus
  - Flournoy, Richard
  - Floyd, John T.
  - Flynn, Edward J.
  - Fobes, Francis H.
  - Food
  - Foote, Walter A.
  - Forbes, W. Cameron
  - Force (Box 168)
  - Force versus humanity
  - Ford, Alexander Hume
  - Ford, Guy Stanton
  - Ford, Henry II
  - Ford, H. D.
  - Ford, James J.
  - Foreign Economic Administration
  - Foreign Economic Administration, business (Wehle, Terry, Emerson, Black, Blaisdell)
  - Foreign investments
  - Foreign Missions Conference
  - Foreign Policy Association, New York, speech by S. K. Hornbeck, 1949 February 19
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1928-1942
  - Foreign Policy Association
  - Foreign Policy, Eisenhower, 1953
  - Foreign Policy, 1953
  - Foreign Policy, Kennan, Berle, 1956
  - Foreign Press Association
  - Foreign Relations
  - Foreign Relations, Volume III, Far East, 1935
  - Foreign Relations, publishing of
  - Foreign Relations (5 folders) (Box 169)
  - Foreign Relations (Box 170)
    - Bibliography, U.S.
    - Department of State, A. N. Young
    - Diplomacy, Count Sforza
    - Diplomacy and international representation and intercourse
    - International differences, methods of settlement short of war
    - Kellogg, diplomacy of
    - Kellogg Pact
    - Scott, J. B.
  - Foreign Relief and Rehabilitations operations
  - Foreign Service
  - Foreign Service Day, 1965 November 12
  - Foreign Service of the United States
  - Foreign Service School, Georgetown University
  - Foreign Service, Training for, Swiggett
  - Foreign Students
    See also: Immigration
  - Foreign trade bibliography
  - Formosa (Box 171)
    - General
    - Maurer, Herrymon, 1955 April
    - Resolution, Mutual Defense Treaty, etc., 1955
    - Reynolds incident and riots, 1957
    - Stevenson on
    - 1965-1966
    - Forrestal, James V. (Box 172)
  - Forsyth, Margaret E.
  - Fortier, Colonel Louis J.
  - Fortune, 1937-1944
  - Forum subjects
  - Fosdick, Raymond B.
  - Foster, Carol H.
  - Four Powers
  - "Fourteen Points," acceptance by Allies
  - Fowler, W. W.
  - Fox, A. Manuel
  - Frakar, Montie R.
  - Frakar, Merlyn R.
  - France
  - France, colonial possessions
  - Francine
  - Franck, Harry A.
  - Frank, Glenn, on Occidental-Oriental relations
  - Franklin, Lynn W.
  - Frazar, E. W.
  - Frazier, Robert
  - Frechtling, Louis E. (Box 173)
  - Fredericksburg, O. H. Darter, 1934 January 19
  - Free, Arthur M.
  - Free movements in United States
  - Freedman, Samuel
  - Freedom of press
  - Freedom of seas
  - Freedom of speech
  - Freedoms Foundation
  - Freeman, Miller
  - Freeman, The
  - French, C. H.
  - French Embassy
  - French Indo-China, 2.0 folders)
  - French Indo-China Military Purchasing Mission
  - French Information Service (Box 174)
  - French orphans
  - Frene letter
  - Frey, Oliver W.
  - Freyn, Hubert
  - Friedinger-Pranter, Robert
  - Friedrich, C. J.
  - Friends of the Land
  - Froclick, Louis D.
  - Fromkes, Mrs. Maurice
  - Fromm, Joe
  - Frost, Wesley
  - Fry, C. Brooks
  - Fulbright, J. William
  - Fulbright Resolution
  - Fuller, Stuart J.
  - Furlong, Colonel Charles Wellington
  - Furniture
  - Furstner, J. Th.
  - Fyfe, J. Howard
  - Gale, Esson M. (2 folders) (Box 175)
  - Gale, Esson and Klinger, R. B., regarding December 8, 1953
  - Galloway, George B.
  - Gallup Poll
  - Gallup Poll, public opinion and the war
  - Gamble, Sidney D.
  - "Gandhi. Mahatma, The World Significance of," John Haynes Holmes, 1922
  - Gann, Dolly, her story
  - Gannett
  - Gardiner, John P.
  - Gardiner, William Howard
  - Gardner, Charles S.
  - Gardner, Edward J.
  - Garfield, Harry A.
  - Garner, James W.
  - Garrels, Arthur
  - Garside, B. A.
  - Gates, Caleb F.
  - Gates, Mary Jean
  - Gauss, Clarence E., 2.0 folders)
  - Gavin, James L.
  - Gavin, James M.
  - Geertsema, C. C.
  - Geissler, Arthur H.
  - Geist, Raymond H. (Box 176)
  - Genealogy forms
  - General Electric Instruction Manual
  - Geneva
  - Geneva Protocol, by Manley O. Hudson, 1924
  - Geneva Representation
  - Genius
  - Genot-Simpson, Marie Janine
  - Gentleman's agreement
  - Gentry, William G.
  - Geopolitics
  - George, Walter F.
  - George Washington University
  - Georgetown University
  - German Colonies, former, disposal in Peace Treaty
  - German Embassy
  - Germany
  - Germany, Adolf Hitler
  - Gest, Guion M.
  - Gewer, W. M.
  - Gibb, John McGregor
  - Gibbon, Elwyn H.
  - Gibson, Hugh
  - Gilbert, Prentiss (Box 177)
  - Gilbert, Prentiss, Observer
  - Gilbert, Rodney, 1963-1964; 4.0 folders)
  - Gilbert, Rodney, 1964-1966 (Box 178)
  - Gilchrist, Huntington, "Germany in China"
  - Gill, D. L.
  - Gilles, H. A.
  - Gilmore, E. A.
  - Gilmore, George W.
  - Ginsberg, Herbert
  - Gipson, Lawrence H.
  - Glass, Meta
  - Glassford, Pelham D.
  - Glassford, William A.
  - Gleason, George
  - Globe Phone Manufacturing Corporation, Reading, Massachusetts
  - Go, Toshi
  - Go-between
  - Godfrey, Stuart C.
  - Godshall, W. Leon
  - Goekooplaan, Adrian
  - Goette, John
  - Gold
  - Golden Book
    See also: Bibliography, One Hundred Choice Books
  - Golden High School, 1903-1904
  - Goldwater, Barry
  - Good, Dorothy
  - Good, J. Carter
  - Good neighbor
  - Goodfellow, M. Preston
  - Goodhart, Professor Arthur
  - Goodnight, Scott (Box 179)
  - Goodrich, L. Carrington, 1963
  - Goodrich, William Lloyd
  - Gordon, Albert H.
  - Gordon, George
  - Gordon, Linley V.
  - Gordon, Peyton
  - Gouda windows
  - Goudriaan, J.
  - Gould, Randall, 2.0 folders)
  - Government agencies, functions of
  - Government Agency of Information and Publicity on Public Affairs (suggested)
  - Government, the business of
  - Government officials, membership in private organizations
  - Government publishers
  - Government service
  - Government, U.S.
  - Gowen, Herbert H.
  - Grady, Henry F.
  - Graeff, Jhr. D. G. de
  - Graham, Bess F. (Box 180)
  - Graham, Malbone W.
  - Graham, William B.
  - Granovsky, Alexander A.
  - Grant Avenue Methodist Church
  - Grant, Hugh Gladney
  - Grant-Smith, U. S.
  - Gravem, Axel B.
  - Gray, Cecil W.
  - Gray, John Henry
  - Gray, Joe
  - Great Britain
    - General
    - British Empire
    - Diplomacy (Box 181)
    - Government
    - Manchuria Incident
    - Policy
    - Relations with United States
    - Sale of destroyers to
    - U.S. controversy, legal and political aspects (lecture)
  - Great Lakes Aircraft Corporation
  - Great Society
  - Green, Joseph C.
  - Green, Leonard N.
  - Green, Theodore F.
  - Greenbie, Sydney
  - Greenbie, Sydney (Box 182)
  - Greenbie, Mrs. Sydney
  - Greene, Albert E.
  - Greene, Jerome D.
  - Greene, Marc T.
  - Greene, Roger S., 3.0 folders)
  - Greene, Winthrop S.
  - Greenland
  - Greensboro, 1952 (Box 183)
  - Gregg, Clifford C.
  - Gregory, Herbert E.
  - Gregory, John H.
  - Grew, Joseph C.
    - General
    - Grew's estimate
    - Correspondence
      - 1932-1935, 4.0 folders) (Box 184)
      - 1936-1938, 6.0 folders) (Box 185)
      - 1939, 4.0 folders) (Box 186)
      - 1940, 3.0 folders) (Box 187)
      - 1941-1942 (Box 188)
      - 1942-1944 (Box 189)
    - Diary
      - May 1934 - July 1936 (Box 190)
      - August 1936 - December 1937 (Box 191)
      - December 1937 - December 1939 (Box 192)
      - January 1940 - December 1940 (Box 193)
      - December 1940 - October 1941 (Box 194)
      - 1941, 3.0 folders) (Box 195)
        Also includes dispatches.
    - Briggs case
    - Grey's "Elegy in a Country Churchyard" (Box 196)
  - Gridiron Club, 1934 April 14
  - Griffin, Eldon
  - Griffith, Ernest S.
  - Griffith, Colonel John S.
  - Griffiths, Austin E.
  - Griffiths, Farnham P.
  - Grigsby, Miss
  - Gripes
  - Griswold, A. Whitney
  - Griswold, Lawrence
  - Groff-Smith, Everitt
  - Grogan, Stanley
  - Gross, Christian
  - Grosscup, Mrs. Ben
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert
  - Grotius, Hugo
  - Group Hospitalization, Inc.
  - Grullemans and Sons, J. J.
  - Guam
  - Guerin, Hubert
  - Guerrillas
  - Guggenheim
  - Gulick, Mrs. Mason
  - Gulick, Sidney, program for China and Japan
  - Gull, E. M.
  - Gunn, Ross
  - Gunnison, Royal Arch
  - Gupta, G. C.
  - Gurner
  - Guru and Ryerson
  - Guthrie, F. P.
  - H., F. (Box 197)
  - H-K Advertising Service, Inc.
  - Haan, Kilsoo
  - Haas, J. J. de
  - Haband Tie Company
  - Habets, Jos. H. C. A.
  - Hacker, Emil C.
  - Hackett, Harold W.
  - Hackworth, Green H.
  - Haering, George J.
  - Haertel, M. H.
  - Hague, The
    See also: The Hague (alphabetized under "T")
  - Hahn, Soon K.
  - Haight, Prof., on "Quarantine"
  - Haines, Colonel Paul H.
  - Hains, Mary J.
  - Haiti
  - Hale, Robert
  - Halifax, Lord (British Ambassador)
  - Halifax and Hornbeck, miscellaneous papers
  - Hall, A. Hamer (Box 198)
  - Hall, H. Duncan
  - Hall, Howard B.
  - Hall, Josef, articles
  - Hall, Josef, "New China,", 1927
  - Hall, Monroe
  - Hall, Noel
  - Hall, Ray Ovid
  - Hall, Victor E.
  - Hallett, Ralph H.
  - Hallock, H. G. C.
  - Ham, Pier van der
  - Hamaker, Frances H.
  - Hamilton, Earl J.
  - Hamilton, George E.
  - Hamilton, George, Rhodes School, 1953
  - Hamilton, Maxwell M., "China in 1931"
  - Hamilton, Maxwell M., correspondence, 3.0 folders)
  - Hamlin, Charles S. (Box 199)
  - Hammerman, S. L.
  - Hampton, Robert
  - Hanchett, David S.
  - Hangchow
  - Hangchow, S. K. Hornbeck at
  - Hangchow Days, S. K. Hornbeck and Goose, 1912
  - Hangchow, Certain Features of the History of Constitution Making, Chekiang Provincial College, 1910
  - Hangchow, Wu, 1961
  - Hankey, Sir M., China, Shantung Hearing, 1919
  - Hankin, Francis
  - Hann, Charles
  - Hannegan, Mr.
  - Hansell, Haywood Shepherd, Jr.
  - Hanson, George C.
  - Harbord, James G.
  - Harbord Mission
    See also: Horneck, S. K., Armenia
  - Harcourt, Brace and Company
  - Hard, Anne - Sketch of S. K. Hornbeck, 1928
  - Hard, Mrs. William
  - Hardenbroek, G. C. D. Baron van
  - Harding, H. F.
  - Harding, Warren G.
  - Haren, Onno C. van
  - Hargrove, William
  - Harkness, William H.
  - Harmon, Francis Stuart
  - Harper and Brothers
  - Harper, David
  - Harper, Samuel N.
  - Harriman, E. A.
  - Harriman, E. H.
  - Harriman, W. Averell
  - Harrington, Dayton M.
  - Harrington, Fred (University of Wisconsin)
  - Harris, Hayden B.
  - Harris, J. Francis
  - Harris (Norman Wait) Institute, 1930, 1939
  - Harris (Norman Wait) Memorial Foundation
  - Harris, Townsend
  - Harrison, Earl G.
  - Harrison, Maurice
  - Harrison, Randolph
  - Hart, A. B.
  - Hart, Boies C.
  - Hart, Sea Island
  - Hart, Charles C. (Box 200)
  - Hart, G. H. C.
  - Hart, Simon
  - Hart, Admiral Thomas Charles
  - Hartley, Hugh H.
  - Hartley, Livingston
  - Hartman, Lillian G.
  - Hartman, Mrs. William
  - Hartzell, Karl D.
  - Harvard
  - Harvard University Library
  - Harvard Club
  - Harvard Club, Roster, 1947
  - Harvard Club of Washington, D. C., 1954
  - Harvard Courses and class records, 1927-1928
  - Harvard University
    - General
    - Exams, History
    - Final grades, 1924-1925
    - S. K. Hornbeck class record, 1925
    - Harvard University Committee on Far Eastern Civilization, 1937-1938 (Box 201)
  - Harvard items
  - Harvard tercentenary
  - Harvey, Paul
  - Harwich-Hook Service
  - Hashimoto, Mt. Tetsuma
  - Haspels, J. C.
  - Hatfield, Dos T.
  - Hatmaker, (Virginia), 1957
  - Hattum, J. W. A. van
  - Hauser, Ernest O.
  - Hausman, William
  - Havana Conference, 1940
  - Hawaii
  - Hawes, Charles H. (Box 202)
  - Hawes, Harry B.
  - Hawkins, H. B., 6.0 folders)
  - Hawkins, Harry C.
  - Hawkins, Paul S.
  - Hawley, John C.
  - Haworth, Mr.
  - Hay, John (Box 203)
  - Hayden, Carl W.
  - Hayden, the Honorable Joseph Ralston
  - Hayes, John D.
  - Hayes, L. Newton
  - Hayes, Ralph
  - Hazard, Henry B.
  - Health check-up, 1945
  - Healy, F. G.
  - Healy, Thomas H., "The Outlook for Disarmament"
  - Hearnshow, F. J. C.
  - Hearst, William Randolph
  - Heater, W. E.
  - Heath, Donald
  - Heest, J. P. Van
  - Heindel, R. H.
  - Heineman, Alfred
  - Heinneman, Mr.
  - Heintzleman, P. Stewart
  - Helder
  - Helfrich
  - Helmick, Judge Milton J.
  - Helmle, William C.
  - Helms, Birch
  - Henderson, A. D.
  - Henderson, Alfred J.
  - Henderson, Archibald
  - Henderson, Horace E.
  - Henderson, Leon
  - Hendrix, Euphanelle
  - Hengstler, Herbert C.
  - Henkle, Charles Zane
  - Henle, Ray
  - Henning, Arthur Sears
  - Henry, James M.
  - Henry, Jules
  - Henry, Robert L.
  - Henry, Robert L. ("Pat")
  - Herod, William R.
  - Heroes of '76
  - Herring, Hubert
  - Herriott, C. D.
  - Herter, Chris, 1966
  - Hewes, Clarence B.
  - Hewes, Thomas
  - Hewitt, Admiral H. K.
  - Heyn, J.
  - Heywood, Florence
  - Hibbard, Frederick P.
  - Hicks, Margaret de Forest, "Japan and Russia in the East"
  - Hievans, Arthur
  - High, Stanley
  - Hight, Frank S.
  - Hildred, William P.
  - Hill, D. J., "The Nations and the Law"
  - Hill, George M.
  - Hill, John A.
  - Hill, L.
  - Hill, Paul A.
  - Hill, Ralph W.
  - Hilsman, Roger
  - Hiltman, J. W.
  - Hiltner, Walter G.
  - Hinckley, Flora (Mrs. Frank E.)
  - Hinckley, Dr. Frank E. (2 folders) (Box 204)
  - Hindmarsh, Albert E.
  - Hines, Frank T.
  - Hinke, Frederick W.
  - Hinkle, Eugene M.
  - Hinshaw, Carl
  - Hinton, Harold C.
  - Hippisley, Alfred E., 2.0 folders)
  - Hirsch, Julius
  - Hishida, Seiji G.
  - Hiss, Alger, 3.0 folders)
  - Hiss, Donald
  - Hiss, Philip H.
  - History
  - History, bibliography, "A Threatened Gap in World History"
  - Histories, Critique on American School Histories
  - Hitchcock, Curtice
  - Hitchcock, Henry B.
  - Hnath, John, 1961-1962 (Box 205)
  - Ho Ping - Song
    See also: China: Ho Ping - Song, SKH Manuscript
  - Ho, Shai Lai, General
  - Hoare, Sir Samuel
  - Hobart, Earle T.
  - Hochschild, H. W.
  - Hochstein, Irma
  - Hocking, William E.
  - Hodges, Charles
  - Hodgins, Eric
  - Hoffman, Milton J.
  - Hoffman, Ross J.
  - Hogue, Richard W.
  - Holoday, William P.
  - Holcomb, Major General Thomas
  - Holcombe, Arthur N.
  - Holland
  - Holland-America Line
  - Holland, Maurice
  - Holland Society, Annual Banquet, 1965 November 10
  - Holland Society, reception to Prince Bernhard, 1966 June 2
  - Holman - Bricker Resolution
  - Holman and Centlivres
  - Holman, Frank, 1950
  - Holman, Frank E. (Attorney at Law)
  - Holmes, George Sanford
  - Holmes, Harry N.
  - Holmes, Julius
  - Holmes, Lieutenant Wilfred J.
  - Holt, E. G.
  - Holt, Ivan Lee
  - Holtom, D. C.
  - Homan, Professor Paul T.
  - Home Craftsman, The
  - Hong Kong (Box 206)
  - Hong Kong, United College of
  - Hook, Sidney
  - Hooton, Earnest A.
  - Hoover, Charles L.
  - Hoover, Herbert, 4.0 folders)
  - Hoover-MacDonald Treaty
  - Hopkins, Frank S.
  - Hopkins, Harry
  - Hopper, Bruce, 4.0 folders)
  - Hopper, W. Earl
  - Horch, Louis L. (Box 207)
  - Hornbeck, Marion A.
  - Hornbeck, Ralph
  - Horner, Charles F.
  - Horton, William E.
  - Hosie, Lady
  - "Hot Pursuit"
  - Hotchkin, Captain Harry
  - Hotel "De Doelen"
  - Hotel Governor Clinton
  - Hotel Pennsylvania
  - Houben, F. J. M. A. H.
  - House, Colonel, notes
  - House, Colonel E. M.
  - House Inquiry
  - House Un-American Activities Committee
  - Houghton, Alanson B.
  - Houston, Herbert S.
  - Howard, Herbert S.
  - Howard, James E.
  - Howard, Roy W.
  - Howard, Stanley F.
  - Howe, William Stuart
  - Howell, G. P.
  - Howland, Charles
  - Howlers
  - Howze, Dr. Charles P.
  - Hoy, Ralph
  - Hsia, C. L.
  - Hsieh, Alice Langley
  - Hsieh, C. K.
  - Hsieh, Dr. Teyhi
  - Hsu, Kathleen, 1966
  - Hu, S. K. Major General
  - Hu Shih, 5.0 folders)
  - Hudson, David (Box 208)
  - Hudson, The Honourable Manley O.
  - Huggins, G. Ellsworth
  - Hughes, Charles Evans
  - Hughes, Edwin H.
  - Hughes, Howard
  - Huisken, Betty
  - Huismans, Mr.
  - Huizinga, Leonard
  - Hull, Cordell, the Julius W. Pratt biography of
  - Hull, Cordell
    - General, 5.0 folders)
    - Memoirs: Hornbeck - Berding correspondence (Box 209)
    - For secretary's speeches
    - Addresses and statements, 1925-1939
    - Addresses and statements, 1940-1942 (Box 210)
    - Birthday, 1951
    - Secretary of State
  - Hull Foundation
  - Hull, John A.
  - Human Events
  - Human Rights
  - Hume, Edgar Erskine
  - Hume, Edward H.
  - Hummel, Arthur W. (Box 211)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H.
  - Humphrey, Mary Churchill
  - Hung, William
  - Hungary
  - Hunnewell, Francis Welles
  - Hunt, William
  - Hunter, Edward
  - Hunter, Frederick M. (Chancellor)
  - Hurd, Colonel
  - Hurja, Emil
  - Hurley, Brigadier General Patrick J.
  - Hurley, George
  - Husband, W. W.
  - Hussey, Harry
  - Husting, Paul O., raising troops, letter to President Wilson
  - Hustinx, Ch. M. J. H.
  - Huston, Jay C.
  - Huston, Dr. John W. (U.S. Naval Academy)
  - Hutchins, Tom
  - Hutchinson, Paul
  - Hyde, Charles Cheney
  - Hyde, Frederic B.
  - Iceland (Box 212)
  - Ickes, Harold L.
  - Ickes Diary
  - Ide, John J.
  - Idealism vs. Realism
  - Ignatieff, Paul
  - Imagination
  - Immigration
  - Imperialism
  - Imperialism, Japan's, evolution of the idea
  - Impossible
  - Inauguration Ceremonies, President Hoover, 1929 March 4
  - Inauguration, 1929
  - Inauguration Ceremony, Ball, etc., 1953
  - Indemnities
  - India
  - India, 1966
  - India (Box 213)
  - Indiscretions
  - Indo-China, 1964
  - Indonesia, East Asia
  - Indonesia, 2.0 folders)
  - Indonesia, 1966 (Box 214)
  - Indonesia, news, 1949
  - Industrialism in Asia and Africa
  - "Inevitability"
  - Information Service Committee
  - Ing, Q. T.
  - "Inquiry,", 1918
  - Insignia
  - Insinger, F. N.
  - Institute of Chinese Culture
  - Institute of International Education
  - Institute of International Education News Bulletin
  - Institute of International Relations, Seattle, 1928
  - Institute of International Relations, University of Southern California, Mission Inn, Riverside, California, 1926
  - Institute of International Relations, Willard Straight Fellowship (Mont Tremblant), 1942; 2.0 folders)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations (8 folders), 1925-1927 (Box 215)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations (7 folders), 1928-1929 (Box 216)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations (9 folders), 1929-1942 (Box 217)
    See also: E. C. Carter
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, Conference, Mont Tremblant (2 folders), 1942 December 4-14 (Box 218)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1935 (Box 219)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1943-1944, 1953, 1960
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, miscellaneous publications
  - Institute of World Organization, 1955 March 17
  - Institutes
  - Institutes of Politics
  - Intelligence
  - Inter-American Bank, The
  - Interests, American
  - Internal Security, testimony of Charles Maynard Cooke
  - International affairs, study of
  - International Apple Association Meeting
  - International Cartels
  - International Chamber of Commerce
  - International Conference of American States (Fourth), reports concerning ratification of conventions
  - International Court of Justice
  - International Court of Justice, Hackworth's Committee, 1944
  - International Digest
  - International education
  - International finance
  - International Justice, World Conference
  - International Law
    - General, 3.0 folders)
    - General (Box 220)
    - Antarctica, sovereignty in
    - Bibliography
    - Bibliography and reference list
    - Calvo and Drago Doctrines and Porter Convention
    - Case books
    - Cases, briefed
    - Cases, current
    - Cases, digested
    - Eastern Asia
      - Ceylon
      - China
      - Malaya
      - Timor, Macao, New Guinea
    - Effects of war on
    - Examination questions
    - Examples
    - Germany: Submarine Controversy, Legal and Political Aspects of, 1916 May 10 (Box 221)
    - Great Britain, 3.0 folders)
    - Great Britain, British blacklist
    - Great Britain, controversies with, 2.0 folders)